



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Telecommunication engineering student with adaptability and curiosity about how things work and new technologies. Good programming logic and ability to solve problems. Experience and knowledge in report design (SSRS), relational databases, object-oriented programming and web development (bootstrap). Currently coursing the MisionTIC program focused on software development. Fast learning and good teamwork skills. Strong Office suite skills and basic GIT knowledge.

EDUCATION

Software developer Student | 2021 - Present MisionTic2022

Telecommunications Engineering | 2019 - Present Universidad de Antioquia – Virtual modality, Colombia

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SIEMPRE.NET S.A.S.

Proyect Leader | 08/01/2019 - Present

- Database administrator.
- Report Designer.
- Internal and external customer support.

SIEMPRE.NET S.A.S.

I.T Support | 20/01/2016 - 20/12/2018

- Data cleaning.
- Database administration.
- Report Designer.
- Customer support.

SIEMPRE.NET

I.T Support | 03/08/2013 - 20/12/2015

- Data cleaning.
- Database administration.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

SQL Python C++ GIT

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native English: Intermediate

REFERENCES

Christian David Moreno

Big Data Engineer 3023505695

Juan Camilo Rivera

Computer Science Engineer 3193543291

INTERESTS

Programming Learn new technologies Video games Music Drawing